duckbrand.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Duck® Brand

Last updated 1/24/14

Thank you for visiting the ShurTech Brands, LLC ("ShurTech") web sites, including but not limited to shurtech.com, duckbrand.com, paintersmategreen.com, frogtape.com, and caremail.com. Below you will find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your personally identifiable information. We have done our best to ensure the privacy and security of your transactions with us.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the content or practices of our web site, you can contact us directly at:

ShurTech Brands, LLC  
Web Site Privacy  
32150 Just Imagine Drive  
Avon, Ohio 44011

**Our Policy**

DuckBrand.com does not collect users' names, physical addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, credit card numbers, driver's license numbers, bank Personal Identification Numbers (PINs), social security numbers, or any other information which can be used to identify a specific person, nor does it match such information with the anonymous profiles, except when placing an order or registering with us. Our web site's technology may record Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses, but does not associate any IP address with an organization name.

Our web sites may gather navigational information about where you go on our web site. This information allows us to see which areas of our web sites are most visited. This helps us improve the quality of visitors' online experiences by recognizing and delivering more of the features and services our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our web site (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site).

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party without your permission.

Any information you provide to us at this site when you establish membership, update an account, shop online or request information (e.g. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information), is maintained in private files on our secure web server and our internal systems. This information is used to enable our web sites to deliver services to you. To ensure compliance with federal law, ShurTech’s web sites do not collect or maintain information provided by children under the age of 14, unless parental consent is obtained.

If you are visiting our web sites from a location outside of the U.S., your connection will be through and to servers located in the U.S. Your orders placed through DuckBrand.com will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from the U.S. and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web server and internal systems located within the U.S.

You should be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our web site, the site or the public. We may, however, use third parties to help us provide services to you, such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, and administering e-mails, drawings or contests. If personally identifiable information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number) is provided to any of these third parties, we will require that such information be maintained by them in strictest confidence.

**Use of Cookies**

DuckBrand.com uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies also allow DuckBrand.com to make our site more responsive to your needs, by delivering better content and merchandise to you. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive and are used by DuckBrand.com to help track your clicks as you go through the pages within the web site. In addition, DuckBrand.com uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping bag and to tell us whether you have previously visited DuckBrand.com. This allows registered users to avoid reentering information upon every new visit to our site. If you register or purchase product through DuckBrand.com, navigational information from previous browsing visits may be associated with the personal information you provide.

**Rate and Review**

From time to time, we may utilize a third party (Bazaarvoice, Inc.) to provide users with the ability to submit reviews, comment on or rate goods, products and services on our website. You should be aware that any information you provide during a “Rate and Review” will be published on a publicly facing website. In addition, cookies are used to access information about users’ browsing patterns in order to help us provide services to you. Information collected during a “Rate and Review” is subject to the Bazaarvoice Privacy Policy. [Click here](http://www.bazaarvoice.com/privacy-policy/) for details. 

**Information We Gather Automatically**

When you visit our Site, we may automatically collect certain non-identifying information about you, such as your movement about the site or the pages on the site you visit most frequently, the type of browser or computer operating system you use or the domain name of the Site from which you linked to us ("Non-identifying Information"). We use this Non-identifying Information internally, to help us enhance the efficiency and usefulness of the Site and to improve customer service.

**Placing an Order**

When you place an order, we will ask you for the following personal information: your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and your credit card number and its expiration date. This information is requested to verify your identify and to process your purchase. Contact information from the order form is only used to send orders. For extra security, DuckBrand.com will never display your full credit card number once it has been entered - We will only reveal the last 4 digits of your credit card for verification purposes.

**Security**

Your contact information is transmitted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, the approved industry standard. We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes.

**Updating Personal Information**

We prefer to keep your personal information accurate and up-to-date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal information including billing and shipping information by logging into Your Account.

**ShurTechWeb Site E-Mail**

When you submit feedback or questions via email, or contact us for information about our web site, we will request your name and email address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries.

DuckBrand.com email updates allow you to receive exclusive information about special offers, events, contests, sweepstakes, new products and much more. If you're not already registered, simply complete our form to receive these special messages. If at any time you would like to stop future delivery of DuckBrand.com emails, please follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each message. Asking to be removed from DuckBrand.com emails will not prevent you from receiving email confirmations for any order you place at DuckBrand.com.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time to time, ShurTech offers surveys or promotions, such as sweepstakes and contests. Participation in these contests or promotions is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, demographic information, phone number and e-mail address. Contest information will be used to conduct drawings, notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used to monitor or improve the site.

**Sweepstakes**

The Sweepstakes entry data that you provide to our web sites, including your name, address, telephone numbers and email address, will be used for your entry into, and the administration of this Sweepstakes. DuckBrand.com may also use this information to send you periodic mailings of promotional or other material. This information will not be shared with other organizations for commercial purposes but may be used by DuckBrand.com or DuckBrand.com's authorized agencies for internal marketing analysis.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our sites may contain links to other sites. ShurTech is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites.

We use industry-standard SSL authentication to guarantee the confidentiality and privacy of online transactions through our site. SSL authentication and 128-bit encryption (scrambling) ensures that your online transaction and credit card information is safe from third party interception.

Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers.

**Disclosure to Authorities**

ShurTech cannot guarantee that all private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right and may be forced to disclose any and all information to government bodies or government officials or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Accordingly, you authorize ShurTech to disclose any and all information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Further, you authorize ShurTech to disclose your password, name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, gray market, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. Specifically, this includes exchanging such information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. ShurTech cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights.

**Your Consent**

By using any of ShurTech’s web sites and the content and services available to you on our sites, you consent to our collection and use of your information as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so that you are always informed of our policies.

**A SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS:**

We respect the privacy of all of our online users, especially children. We do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. Our policy is intended to adhere to the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) privacy guidelines. We encourage parents to monitor, supervise and join their children in online activities.
